

4209 QUE BALAG STREET, BARANGAY UGONG VALENZUELA CITY, PH, 1440 (+63) 9055629640 radiantcjuan@gmail.com

RADIANT C. JUAN

Full Stack Web Developer

SKILLS

In my 8 years of experience as a Web Developer, I have the necessary skill set and knowledge to help your company to be profitable. My mission is to deliver operational excellence, productivity, and compliance to ensure and maximize client services, minimize costs they serve and most importantly drive revenue for their business.

Coding

Scripting

PHP Laravel CakePHP Drupal Wordpress

Database

MongoDB MySQL MSSQLServer

JavaScript

jQuery React JS

Ionic with React

CSS

CSS3 Bootstrap Sass Less

Operating System

Linux, Mac, Windows

Repositories and Versioning

AGILE, Atlassian, CI/CD, TDD

Cloud Administration and Analytics

Amazon
Apache
Nginx
Cpanel
Plesk
DataDog
Tealium
Google Tag Manager
Google Analytics

Repositories and Versioning

Git, BitBucket, GitHub, GitLab

EXPERIENCE

Diversify (Temple and Webster Microsourcing (HungryHungry client)

Position: Full-Stack Engineer Location: Taguig, Philippines

Duration: JANUARY 25, 2021 - PRESENT

With the position of Full-stack Engineer, I handle the development, implementation, management, optimization and continuous improvement of the Temple And Webster online furniture shop based in Australia.

client)

Position: PHP Developer Location: Pasig, Philippines

Duration: MAY 15, 2017 - JANUARY 22,

Back-end developer of Ordermate Online website, an online ordering multi-site application where merchant can freely self-manage their content for their online ordering site section, Ordermate Online is owned by an Australian Company based in Melbourne named Ordermate, I do the back end development, API integration, third party app integration, server configuration for Ordermate Online and all back-end related.

IBM Solutions Delivery Inc.

Position: Web Applications Developer Location: Quezon City, Philippines Duration: SEPT 2015 - APR 2017

- Transitioned from ABS-CBN to IBM
- Web developer for IBM's ABS-CBN induction deck project
- Responsible for back-end development for all the websites of ABS-CBN's TV network

Affinity X

Position: Web Developer

Location: Quezon City, Philippines Duration: SEPT 2014 - SEPT 2015

- Web Developer & Designer
- Email Marketing Advertisements Designer

Chaboba Supply Ordering and Inventory System

https://orders.chaboba.ph/

Supply ordering and inventory system for Chaboba Milk Tea shop franchise, this website lets the franchisees of Chaboba order their needed supply, this also helps the Franchiser to track their inventory and print receipts

Work Type: One time freelance project

Responsibilities:

- Build the website's back-end and front-end implementation from ground up
- Planning
- Server setup
- Database setup
- Security Implementation
- Yearly maintenance
- Design

Manila Water

https://www.manilawater.com/

A multi page website with various web app inside that tells everything about Manila Water Company

Work Type: One time freelance project

Responsibilities:

- Build the website's back-end and front-end implementation from ground up
- Planning
- Server setup
- Database setup
- Security Implementation
- Yearly maintenance

Laguna Water

https://www.lagunawater.com.ph/

A multi page website with various web app inside that tells everything about Laguna Water Company

Work Type: One time freelance project

Responsibilities:

- Build the website's back-end and front-end implementation from ground up
- Planning
- Server setup
- Database setup
- Security Implementation
- Yearly maintenance

S.P.A.R.T.A.

Local Application

Sales' Performance, Achievements, and Rewards Tracking App (SPARTA), a web application analytics for sales's performance.

Work Type: Employment

Responsibilities:

 Build the website, custom CMS, and front-end implementation from ground up

Hungryhungry (formerly: Ordermate Online) Admin

https://admin.ordermate.online/

A web application admin for multiple site restaurants where they can self manage their Online Ordering websites.

Work Type: Employment

Responsibilities:

- Web app maintenance
- Backend new feature development and maintenance
- Server administration
- Admin's front-end new feature development and maintenance
- API development for front-end online ordering web application

Light Force

https://www.lightforce.com/

An ecommerce wordpress website for a company based in Australia where it sells lights for off road vehicles and hunting.

Work Type: Freelance

Responsibilities:

- Maintenance
- New design development

Binbrook Plumbing

http://binbrookplumbing.ca/

A portfolio website made in wordpress for a Canadian Plumbing Company where they showcase their expertise in Plumbing.

Work Type: Employment

Responsibilities:

 Build the website from ground up using pre-built templates

Nature Play

https://www.natureplayqld.org.au/

A wordpress website for children in south australia to experience nature where you can book or join an event.

Work Type: Freelance

Responsibilities:

• Website Maintenance

APRS

https://aprsrifles.com.au/

Ace Precision Rifle Systems, an ecommerce wordpress website for a company based in Australia where it sells rifles and offers gunsmithing, and sister company of lightforce.

Work Type: Freelance

Responsibilities:

• Website Maintenance

Summit Doors

https://summitdoors.com.au/

An e-commerce website that sells doors based in Australia.

Work Type: Freelance

Responsibilities:

• Website Maintenance

EDUCATION

FEU - East Asia College, Manila — BS Computer Science Major in Software Engineering

MAY 2010 - APRIL 2014, Nicanor Reyes St., Sampaloc, Manila, Philippines

Accomplishments and applications developed:

• Kaidoku: Japanese character image recognizer and translator Android mobile application

An image processing mobile app that uses Tesseract Optical Character Recognition to recognize Japanese character from a raw image, convert it into a text data and translate the recognized text into English as my latest project.

• Health Buff Assistant: health and fitness Android mobile application

Developed using Android Development Tools as a thesis project by doing basic research, which improved my skills and techniques in Android and Java programming and in project managing